>> Jem Young: 我们将以命令行开头。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: We'll start
with the command line.
有人知道什么是命令行吗 ?
Anybody know what command line is?
假设每个人都可以
Assuming everybody.
是啊看起来像这样
Yeah, it looks something like this.
我要换个开关
I'm gonna switch over.
所以我可以跟你打声招呼
So I can say, echo hi.
什么 ?
Says, hi.
在这里做遇回的东西
Groundbreaking stuff here.
我们今天要做的事都在指挥线上
A lot of what we're gonna do
today is on the command line.
实际上我们今天要做的事都在指挥线上
Actually, most of what we're gonna
do today is on the command line.
这对人们是有点吓人的
And it's a little intimidating for people.
特别是你只是在用你的鼠标，检查这些东西。
Especially if you're just using your mouse
and inspecting and all these things.
但到了最后你会喜欢这条命令行的
But by the end of the day,
you're gonna love the command line.
你会看到它很强大，它是可重复的。
You'll see it's so powerful,
it's so repeatable.
真的，你现在就可以把那只老鼠扔出去。
And really, you can just throw
that mouse out right now.
有人有老鼠吗
Anybody have a mouse?
不开玩笑的
No, just kidding.
别在家里这么做
Don't do that at home.
我不想被怪罪
I don't wanna get blamed for that.
但今天我们对指挥线路会很满意
But today we're gonna be really
comfortable with command line.
我们会看到，它只是一个用户界面，就像其他的一样。
And we're gonna see, it's just a user
interface, just like anything else.
>> Jem Young: 为什么命令行?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So why the command line?
有人知道为什么指挥线路吗
Anybody, why the command line?
我今天要问很多问题只要习惯就好
I'm gonna ask a lot of questions today,
so just get used to it.
等等我已经听你说过了
Wait, I already heard from you.
泰勒
Taylor?
>> 扬声器 2: 并非所有服务器都有一个 GUI。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Not all
servers even have a GUI.
>> Jem Young: 是的，好的答案，这完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yes, good answer,
that's exactly right.
>> 扬声器 3: 没有限制。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: There's just no limitation.
>> Jem Young: 完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Exactly.
>> 演讲者 3: 不管如何设计一个 GUI ，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: No matter how
well designed a GUI is,
你不能把所有的可能性都包括在内
you just cannot encompass
all the possibilities.
>> Jem Young: 是。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yes.
>> 扬声器 3: 可以在命令行中使用。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: That are capable
in a command line.
>> Jem Young: 完美，伟大的答案，每个人。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Perfect,
great answers, everyone.
我喜欢你这么说的 GUI
And I love that you all said GUI.
GUI 代表图形用户界面，对于不熟悉的用户和
GUI stands for graphical user interface,
for those who are unfamiliar and
从来没见过
never seen it.
但是 GUIs 已被视化。
But GUIs are opinionated.
是有人对用户应该看到的内容的看法
It's someone's opinion about what
exactly the user should see and
他们应该如何与之互动
how they should interact with that.
它的布局是完全背景的。
And how its laid out is
completely contextual.
在另一个国家，也许我根本不理解他们的 GUI 。
In a different country, maybe I
wouldn't understand their GUI at all.
因为我习惯了这边的按钮而不是这边
Because I'm used to the buttons being
on this side instead of this side.
命令行无所不在。
The command line is ubiquitous.
命令行在每个国家或地区使用每种语言。
The command line works in every
language in every country.
每个操作系统都有一个命令行，无论是 Windows， Mac还是 Linux。
Every operating system has a command line,
whether it Windows, Mac, or Linux.
他们都有指挥线路
They all have command lines.
如果你精通指挥的话如果你真的很擅长
And if you're proficient at the command
line, if you're really good,
我在这层附近没有地方所以我不会说你会更快
I'm nowhere near this level, so
[LAUGH] I won't say that you'll be faster.
但通常来说，在命令行上做得更快。
But it is faster doing things on
the command line, generally speaking.
它是一致的，命令行总是一致的。
It's consistent, the command
line's always gonna be the same.
如果我们讨论的是 Linux，这些命令通常是一样的。
The commands are generally gonna be
the same, if we're talking about Linux.
说实话，剧本更容易做，比 GUIs 更容易自动化。
And honestly, it's easier to script,
it's easier to automate than GUIs.
您可以编写 GUI 来自动执行鼠标移动以及所有其他操作。
And you can write GUIs to automate mouse
movements and all these other things.
但命令行就是它的力量所在
But the command line is just,
it's where the power's at.
最初，当计算机首次被发明时，它是所有人都拥有的。
And originally, when computers were
first invented, it's all people had.
> > Jem Young: 我们把它放在那里。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: We'll just keep it there.
所有这些都是接入命令线路的终端。
All they had were were terminals
which access command line.
而且没有一个 GUI之类的东西。
And there was no such thing as a GUI.
这就是为什么 Windows 3.1 和 Mac ，以及所有这些
That's why Windows 3.1 and Mac,
and all these things we take for
被揭露的事实
granted now, were revelations.
因为它使计算机变得更容易获取。
Because it made computers more accessible.
但如果你回到过去的学校
But if you go back to the old school days,
硬盘上的平台是你能旋转的
the place where platters on hard
drives were this big you could spin
手动获取您需要访问该数据的确切位置。
them manually to get exactly where
you needed to be to access that data.
这些人都是用指挥线路和 GUIs 就像，哇，
Those people were all using command
line and GUIs were just like, wow,
那就太好了也许有一天
that'd be fantastic, maybe someday.